Okay, now it's time to write a claw.md.
And you know, there's no there's no
secret here that that you need to put
work into your claude.md to get it right
for your project that of course it's
tempting just to do like a rough loop or
something, just give it a one sentence,
let it go. But if we're trying to build
a strong project here, this is our
opportunity to influence like the boss.
This is where we put our our human
element behind it and make something
that's really differentiated. So look,
I've just I've just written this
claw.md. Let's take a look at it. The
pre-legal project. This is a SAS product
to allow users to draft legal agreements
based on templates in the templates
directory. The user can carry a chat in
order to establish what document they
want and how to fill in the fields. The
available documents are covered in
catalog.json file in the project route
included here. And then I've done this
thing here at and then something. If you
do that, I think I mentioned this before
a while back. If you do that, it inserts
that file and this can be like a fully
like a long path to something or in this
case catalog.json is just in the project
route. Then that just gets shoved in
there in the file. I remember I told you
about this when I said you could have an
agents.mmd that this could just refer
to. So that's why I'm doing that here.
It's a great trick to know about. And
then I'm just giving it the context. The
initial implementation is a front-end
only prototype just so that it
understands what's going on. Okay. So
that's the overview. And you'll notice I
haven't given it all the business
requirements because we're going to use
Jira for that. But I've given it the
overall context so that the it's it's
clear. There's there's it's it's easy to
be coherent when it knows what the game
is. And then I've got a section that's
called development process which is just
saying use your Atlassian tools to read
the feature instructions from Jura.
Develop the feature. Do not skip any
steps. You just factor in what we've
already learned. Thoroughly test the
feature with unit test and integration
test. Fix any issues. Submit a PR using
your GitHub tools. And now for AI
design. I've put in these two sections.
AI design technical design. When writing
code to make calls to LMS, use your
Cerebrass skill. What's that you're
wondering? To use light NLM via Open
Router to the GPT OSS120B model with
Cerebrass as the inference provider, you
should use structured outputs so you can
interpret the results and populate
fields in the legal document. Well, so
you're thinking, I'm going to add in a
skill called Cerebrass that's going to
make all of this clear. Well, I hope I'm
going to maybe we're going to do that
together in a second. Technical design.
The entire project should be packaged
into a Docker container. The back end
should be in backend slash and be a UV
project using fast API. The front end
should be fast frontend slash consider
stat. This is this is similar to what we
said last time. There should be scripts
like this. Now, I noticed you can see
there that one of the funny things about
markdown, I put this as separate lines,
but it doesn't put them as separate
lines when you look at the preview. To
do that, you have to put two spaces at
the end of each line like this. Oops.
And now it's turned that into a full
stop by default.
Um, and then this. Now, if we now look
at the preview, you're wondering what I
just did. Save that. Rightclick. Open
preview. Now, you're going to see that
this technical design is laid out much
more nicely. That's what I wanted. And
then these are the start and stop
scripts. And that's where the back end
will then be running. And I shoved my
color scheme in at the very end with my
personal favorite brand colors, the ones
from the slide deck. So that is where we
are. That's laid out a nice claude.md.
Do we have anything else to do before we
start? Well, yes, we have to make this
skill. Okay. So, we're going to make a
new skill. It's going to be a skill that
anyone on our project, our other team
members will be able to use, too,
because it's going to be an important
skill for this SAS product. and it's
going to be a skill that's about calling
an LLM, but I want to call an LLM in a
particular way. For this product, what I
really care about is that I want the
responses to be incredibly fast. I want
the LLM to respond bam really quickly.
And to do that, I'm going to use an
open-source model, GPT OSS120, and I'm
going to use it over open router as
we've done before, which is great. But
I'm going to with open router, I'm going
to specify I want it to use one of the
providers. In particular, I want to use
a provider called Cerebrass, which is
super fast. Uh you pay a little bit
more. You It's still quite cheap, but
it's a little bit more than than uh than
the normal uh for for GP OSS120, but as
a result, you get stuff really really
fast. Now, you may want to stick with
free models. You may not want to do
this, in which case, just skip this part
or change the skill to something
different. But that's what I'm going to
do to demonstrate creating our own
skill. And also while I'm at it, show
you Cerebras. So I'm going into the
Claude directory. I'm making a new
folder and I'm calling it skills. And
then I'm going to make a new folder in
here. And this folder is what you call
the name of your skill. I'm going to
call it surass.
There it is. That is my new skill. And
now within that, I'm making a new file.
And that new file is going to be the one
that's going to have the the the agent
skill itself, which is skill.md.
This is where we begin. Okay. And at the
top of the file, skill.md, you have to
put something in with this exact format.
And look, it's a bit like API keys. You
got to get this format right. If you get
it wrong, it won't work. And you know, I
I'm here to help you. I'll I'll help you
if you get stuck, but it's very hard for
me to debug that remotely. It's it's the
best thing to do is to just get it
right. Uh so using this format um and of
course I'll have this in the in the
course resources but you can we're now
going to give it a name. We're going to
call it cerebrass.
Um it's going to be the cerebras
inference we'll call it. Um uh use this
to write
code to call an LLM
uh using light llm and open router
with the cerebras
inference provider.
There we go. That's very clear. That's
exactly what we're going to do with this
skill. I'll save it so that dot
disappears. That is the meta data for
the skill. Okay. And now to paste in the
the skill itself. And I've just written
this and obviously take care of these
things. But but I'm going to put this in
the course resources of course. And uh
let me just just quickly show it to you.
I'll open it as a preview so you can see
what this is. Calling an LLM via
Cerebrass. These instructions allow you
to write code to call an LLM with
Cerebra specified as the inference
provider. And then there's some setup
that tells it what to do. And then code
snippets, some imports and constants,
code to call Cerebrass, code to call
Cerebras for structured outputs. And
there is some clear code, some good
examples, very simple, clearly
explained. That should be all it takes
to add our own skill. Now, we're pretty
much ready to go. Just a couple more
things to do. I just want to make this
model clear to in our claw.md and tell
it one more thing and then we're ready
to go. So back we go over to the claw.md
and over here I just in this AI design
uh I want to make it clear that we're
going to be using the model that we've
got. Let's just uh um put this in here.
Um hang on let me delete that. We'll use
back ticks in in markdown to show code.
I'm going to put that in there for that
model to the OpenAI GPT OSS120B model
with Cerebras as the inference provider.
That seems clear. Okay. And then one
more thing we got to do. Do you know
what that is? We we have to add our EMV
file with our open router key that we
set up before. I can just copy it across
into here. I'm going to do that right
now and you should do it too. And the
simplest way to do that is to bring up a
new terminal. We're in pre-legal here
and we just do cp for copy. Want to go
up one directory. We want to go into the
directory that's called PM and we want
to take the EMV file that's there and we
want to copy that right here in this
current directory. Bam. The MV file has
appeared. I'm not going to double click
on it because then you'll see my key.
But hopefully you've done that and
you've checked it and it's got open
router API key spelled right in there.
And then as a final step uh just check
that we have explained here that that
key uh just in case we um uh we'll just
make that absolutely crystal clear. Um
there is an open router API key in the
MV file in the project routt. Done.
Okay. So it's super clear now. We've got
everything laid out. We've got a claw.md
in our home directory. We've got one
here. We've got a MV file and we've even
added a new skill for Cerebrass and
we've told it to use that skill in order
to do do what we need. So, we're all
ready now to build our SAS application.
Oh, not so fast. I think I forgot one
thing in the technical design. I want to
say that it should use a database that
it sets up in the docker container just
as we did before with the PM project. If
you want to use a proper database like
use superbase or something to have an
API database then you should definitely
do that. If you've taken my ML ops
course or of my NA course, you know how
to do these these kinds of things using
Clark or Superbase. But I'm I'm going to
um keep it simple for this and just say
uh the the back end the front end um the
database
should use SQL light and be created
uh from from scratch each time the uh
Docker container
is brought up
allowing
for a users table with sign up and sign
in. Okay, that's a very simple extra
directive we'll put in there. Leave that
there. So, it's got that information
too. And now I believe that we're